

KANISORN KAMPRAPHAI

นาย คณิสร คำประไพ

PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of birth: 26 october 1998

Age: 24

Nationality: Thai

Determined to develop their own abilities in a suitable future job. Love to learn and try new things of interest. enjoy finding experiences in life that increase my opportunities for growth.

EDUCATION

King Mongkut's Institute of Technology Ladkrabang Bachelor in Economics for Business. 2017-2021

- Chief Equipment and Purchasing Department of Student club
- Database SQL and Python

ENGLISH SKILL

Listening: High Writing: High speaking: Medium

CONTACT



yeenyeen41@gmail.com



088-1953359



yeenkampraphai

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATION

- Communication coordination
- Digital marketing (Facebook Instragram Line)
- accounting
- Marketing and statistics analyse with the SPSS.
- Excel, Word, PowerPoint, Photoshop, Illustrator
- SQL and Python

WORK EXPERIENCE

Universal wings, Co-Manager and Co-Owner

AUGUST 2018 - JUNE 2019

- Purchase of materials and ingredients
- Take care of the staff to Work efficiently
- Inspect and control food quality, raw materials, services and
- Make offline and online marketing to increase
- Planning the production of the highest quality.

KMITL Business school, Internship

JUNE 2020 - JULY 2020

- make digital marketing such as graphic info, Instruction video
- Coordinate with each department that makes the operation faster

Time consult, Research Assistant

MARCH 2021 - JUNE 2022

- Call to coordinate with Government agency to provide details and invite to the meeting
- Save the progress and makes keeping track of tasks easy
- Inform the progress and update the information.



BorntoDev

CERTIFICATE OF GRADUATION

Awarded To

KANISORN KAMPRAPHAI

Graduating From

Essential SQL for Everyone

Date: 2022-06-11

Serial No.

cert_vbd43s45

